# **MANUEL VILLAR VITORIA**



-- FULL STACK DEVELOPER --

# CONTACT

- (+34) 638 654 352
- manu.villar.vitoria@gmail.com
- in <u>Linkedin</u>
- Project Portfolio
- 08032, Barcelona. Spain

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- REACT (Hooks) | NEXT.js (SSR) | REDUX |
  Material UI | Styled Components |
  Emotion | Storybook.
- Javascript (ES6+) | TypeScript | Fetch API | Async/Await | Axios | Webpack | NPM.
- HTML5 | CSS3 ( Flexbox, Grid... ) | SASS | Bootstrap 5 | Materialize | Tailwindcss.
- Node.js | Express.js | Mongoose | Cluster |
  API Gateway | REST APIs | Websockets |
  Microservices | Firebase | MongoDB |
  Postman | Swagger.
- Testing (Jest | Enzyme | Cypress)
- Agil (GIT | Github | Gitlab | Scrum | Trello |
  JIRA | Slack | Microsoft Teams )
- DevOps (VPS | Linux | AWS | Nginx | Docker )
- SEO (Google Analytics | Search Console | Semrush | Sistrix | Ahrefs )

# SOFT SKILLS

- Commercial & Communicative.
- Responsible & Organized.
- Teamwork & Agile Methodologies.
- Problem Solving & Agil Mindset.
- Motivated & Self-taught.
- Proactive & Disciplined.
- Search for excellence at work.

# ABOUT ME

Frontend Developer or Full Stack Developer **specialized in Javascript**, with **great enthusiasm and passion** for this world of web development. Always in **constant learning** and willing to train in new programming languages and develop my skills to grow professionally.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Javascript Developer in Accenture**

MARCH 2021 - MAY 2021 (3 MONTHS)

 Developing new features in javascript for the client Zurich, working in agile methodologies ( JIRA, Scrum, Git, Github & SourceTree ) and in a mixed English-Spanish team.

# **Frontend Developer in APPTO**

DECEMBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021 (3 MONTHS)

- Development and maintenance of the Frontend of a real App, which reads texts stored in an API -<u>Compartiendo el Pan</u> -. All of this working in a team with 2 developers more using agil methodologies.
- Frontend Stack: REACT, REDUX, StoryBook, Styled Components, Git, Gitlab, Scrum, Trello & Docker.

# Frontend Developer & SEO Specialist in SF Abogados SEPTEMBER 2020 - DECEMBER 2020 ( 3 MONTHS)

 Maintenance of existing websites and development of new websites and landings. Optimization of the architecture, web content and prevention - solution of Google penalties. Web analytics with Google Analytics, Search Console & Semrush.

# TRAINING

- Full Stack Web Bootcamp (**KEEPCODING** Finishing-)
- Courses Web Developer (**Udemy Academy** Currently )
- Master in Marketing Digital & E-commerce ( EAE Business School - 2019 -)
- Course INEM Web Development( Asedem- CdPs N-3 (IFCD0210) - 2017 - )
- Degree in Technical Architecture ( **EPSEB-UPC** -2013-)

#### LANGUAGES

• English: B1 - B2

• Catalan: Native